Guide to the David Trinidad Papers ca. 1970-2002 MSS.106
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Accretions 2002. Series IV
  - Subseries H: Notebooks 1984-2002
    - Notebook. December 2001. (Box 2002.1, Folder 5)
  - Subseries I: Date Book 1987-2002
    - Datebook., 1999 (Box 2002.1, Folder 1)
    - Datebook., 2000 (Box 2002.1, Folder 2)
  - Subseries J: Photographs
    - Photographs. Childhood., undated (Box 2002.11, Folder data_value_missing_25533f300cbff989f55f9f0f29653888)
    - Photographs. Childhood., undated (Box 2002.12, Folder data_value_missing_5a1a0e819cfd465b895fa7fd737fe1db)
    - Photographs., ca. 1970 (Box 2002.13, Folder data_value_missing_ef064def3f0b1c6115cbcb3325d1c52a)
    - Photographs. Family., undated (Box 2002.14, Folder data_value_missing_51d5566ac14dfe87bf850928b5d2f36d)
    - Photographs. Family, undated (Box 2002.15, Folder data_value_missing_60ee004739496e03d11e3f6d9e2a4f95)
    - Photographs., 1988-1989 (Box 2002.16, Folder data_value_missing_d4fe7eb23791fe171b691e7c1b8bea06)
    - Photographs., 1990 (Box 2002.17, Folder data_value_missing_60427cd482384498d18b9ec18da88f30)
    - Photographs., 1990-1992 (Box 2002.18, Folder data_value_missing_b16fb26a65db5df3314b464e6263ff1a)
    - Photographs., ca. 1993 (Box 2002.19, Folder data_value_missing_6df1e76859d00da8a5ba4fca30bceecf)
    - Photographs., ca. 1999 (Box 2002.20, Folder data_value_missing_4111939c7ee0132eea4f371bef66ac03)
    - Photographs. DT headshots, group shots, friends, undated (Box 2002.21, Folder data_value_missing_7333415891d33de52ad9f66c532dafe4)
    - Photographs. Literary friends, undated (Box 2002.22, Folder data_value_missing_f34d54a7fe7f56a9fae1f513cf6f1214)
    - Photographs. Jacqueline Susann, undated (Box 2002.23, Folder data_value_missing_36be991389261fa08f62b8c97aed11f0)
    - Photographs. Barbie Doll Collection, undated (Box 2002.24, Folder data_value_missing_881f7722a22f4b08e3d3296d93653d91)
  - Subseries K: Videos
    - Jackie Special: Valley, VHS, undated (Box 2002.25, Folder 1)
    - The Other Jackie, Grove Press/New School. October 21, 1997, VHS (Box 2002.25, Folder 2)
    - Valley of the Dolls, "Original Costume Test," VHS, undated (Box 2002.25, Folder 3)
    - Intimate Portrait: Jacqueline Susann, September 7, 1999, VHS (Box 2002.25, Folder 4)
    - E! Hollywood Story, Jacqueline Susann. May 9, 1999 (Box 2002.25, Folder 5)
  - Subseries L: Audio Recordings
    - DT and Rachel Sherwook, KCSN Radio, November 29, 1978. Audio Cassette (Box 2002.25, Folder 1)
    - DT and Rachel Sherwood. "Night and Fog," "Gift of Dionysus," original. Audio Cassette, undated (Box 2002.25, Folder 2)
    - DT and Rachel Sherwood. "Night and Fog," "Gift of Dionysus," dubbed May 12, 1997. Audio Cassette (Box 2002.25, Folder 3)
    - DT and Rachel Sherwood on KCSN Radio, November 29, 1978. Audio Cassette (Box 2002.25, Folder 4)
    - DT and Rachel Sherwood. 11 Poems. Dubbed May 12, 1997. Audio Cassette (Box 2002.25, Folder 5)
    - DT, KCRW, October 265, 1984. Audio Cassette (Box 2002.25, Folder 6)
    - James Schuyler, "Fresh Fuit Radion," Minneapolis, November 6, 1986. Audio Cassette (Box 2002.25, Folder 7)
    - DT and Skelley. April 9, 1987. Audio Cassette (Box 2002.25, Folder 8)
    - DT, Bookworm. KCRW. June 12, 1989. Audio Cassette. (Box 2002.25, Folder 9)
    - DT, The Loft. Minneapolis, MN. June 30, 1989. Audio Cassette. (Box 2002.25, Folder 10)
    - DT, LAS. February 22, 1991. Audio Cassette. (Box 2002.26, Folder 11)
    - DT, World AIDS Day. Fresh Air. December 1, 1994. Audio Cassette. (Box 2002.26, Folder 12)
    - Barbie, Radio Times. March 2, 1999. Audio Cassette. (Box 2002.26, Folder 13)
    - DT, WBFO Radio. Buffalo, NY. Audio Cassette., undated (Box 2002.26, Folder 14)
    - DT, "Fresh Fruid," KFAI-FM. Audio Cassette., undated (Box 2002.26, Folder 15)
    - "Pavane" and "My Cousin is a Porno Star." Audio Cassette., undated (Box 2002.26, Folder 16)
    - Out Write Conference, "Self Censorship and Personal Revelation." Audio Cassette., undated (Box 2002.26, Folder 17)
    - Poetry Tape. Brainard, Plath, Dlugos, Gerstler, Cooper, etc. Audio Cassette, undated (Box 2002.26, Folder 18)
  - Subseries M: Childhood Material
    - Family Tree, undated (Box 2002.27, Folder 1)
    - Grade School Progress Reports and Report Cards, undated (Box 2002.27, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook. Birth to 1974 [located in oversize box], 1970-1974 (Box 2002.27, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook. 1974-1978. [located in oversize box] (Box 2002.27, Folder 4)
  - Subseries O: Joyce Trinidad
    - Baby Book., undated (Box 2002.27, Folder 1)
    - Early Photographs in two photo albums., undated (Box 2002.31)
    - Autograph book., undated (Box 2002.27, Folder 3)
    - High School Yearbook., undated (Box 2002.27, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence. from grandmother., undated (Box 2002.27, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence. from grandparents., undated (Box 2002.27, Folder 6)
    - Grandmother. Misc., undated (Box 2002.27, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence. Joyce and Rupert Trinidad., undated (Box 2002.27, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence. Joyce and Rupert Trinidad., undated (Box 2002.27, Folder 9)
    - Cards to Joyce Trinidad. misc., undated (Box 2002.27, Folder 10)
    - Cards to Joyce Trinidad. Misc., undated (Box 2002.27, Folder 11)
    - Cards to Joyce Trinidad. Misc., undated (Box 2002.27, Folder 12)
    - High School., undated (Box 2002.27, Folder 13)
    - High School, undated (Box 2002.27, Folder 14)
    - High School Graduation., undated (Box 2002.27, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous., undated (Box 2002.27, Folder 16)
    - Scrapbook. "To My 'Momma'" from DT, undated (Box 2002.27, Folder 17)
- Accretions 2002. Oversize Materials
  - Valley of the Dolls. Promotional Material., undated (Box 2002.28, Folder data_value_missing_be040d419e7c236d71c31041ba6ce354)
  - Scrapbook. Birth to 1974, 1970-1974 (Box 2002.29, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook., 1974-1978 (Box 2002.29, Folder 3)
  - Early Photographs. Joyce Trinidad., undated (Box 2002.29, Folder 3)
  - Theme from Valley of the Dolls Sheet Music. [Flat], undated (Box 2002.30, Folder 5)
  - Dogs, Dames, and Dolls. Early Proofs. [flat], undated (Box 2002.30, Folder 6)
  - Writers at Rutgers, 1996 Posters [flat] (Box 2002.30, Folder 7)
  - Writers at Rutgers. 1997 Posters. [flat] (Box 2002.30, Folder 8)
  - Writers at Rutgers. 1998 Posters. [flat] (Box 2002.30, Folder 9)
  - Writers at Rutgers. 1999 Posters [flat] (Box 2002.30, Folder 10)
  - Writers at Rutgers. 2000 Posters [flat] (Box 2002.30, Folder 11)
  - Writers at Rutgers. 2001 Posters [flat] (Box 2002.30, Folder 12)
- Accretion 2012. Series IV, Subseries J: Photographs
  - Box-mounted photographs of Barbie printed from slides by Trinidad. Created for exhibition Downtown Pix at the Greay Gallery., 2012 (Box 2012.32)
  - Box-mounted photographs of Barbie printed from slides by Trinidad. Created for exhibition Downtown Pix at the Greay Gallery. (Box 2012.33)
- Unprocessed Scripts, 1990-2009 (Box 16)